<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss>
    <channel>
        <item>
            <id>1320</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Cedefop labour and skills shortage index</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9202</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How employment growth, replacement needs and skills imbalances will affect EU labour markets&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 08:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1321</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Evolution of European skills systems </title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9199</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The European skills index shows how national skills systems responded during the challenging period of 2015 to 2022.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 12:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1322</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Moving towards common policy goals and aligned progress reporting</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9198</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p class="MsoNormal"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span lang="EN-GB"&amp;gt;Building on years of joint work within the Copenhagen Process, European countries have now committed to common priorities lai&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 07:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1323</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Monitoring and evaluating lifelong guidance systems across Europe</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9196</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Traditional learning and career pathways are being replaced by more dynamic, ‘patchier’ routes and shorter job tenures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 09:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1324</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Microcredentials: striving to combine credibility and agility</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9192</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Microcredentials hold promise for connecting people’s skillsets with labour market demand in a rapidly changing world of work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 08:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1325</id>
            <title>Briefing note - From ‘greenovators’ to ‘green’ minds: key occupations for the green transition</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9189</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Green occupations encompass not only those powering ‘green’ technological change and infrastructure, but also those that support the shift towards new, more circular sustainable EU economi&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1326</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Lifelong guidance for persons with disabilities</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9186</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cedefop, together with its CareersNet partners in EU Member States and beyond, has collected examples of lifelong guidance policies and practices that support the rights and opportunities &lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 14:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1327</id>
            <title>Briefing note – Big skills for small companies</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9183</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This briefing note takes stock of policies and instruments EU countries deploy to encourage MSME training provision and to strengthen their training performance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1328</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Working together towards attractive, inclusive, innovative, agile and flexible VET</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9180</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the framework of European countries’ cooperation on VET and lifelong learning, Cedefop monitors, analyses and reports on countries’ priorities and activities.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1329</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Ready, steady, go!</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9179</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cedefop 2022-23 activities help kickstart the European Year of Skills.&amp;amp;nbsp;In a context of crisis and accelerating megatrends, the Agency continues to focus attention on the vocationa&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1330</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Looking back to look ahead: what is the future for VET in Europe?</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9178</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the current, fast-changing education and labour market landscape, there is a need to promote more learner-centred strategies and to build bridges between initial and continuing vocation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1331</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Empowering teachers and trainers to manage change</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9177</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The professional development of vocational education and training (VET) teachers and trainers is crucial to helping them perform their many tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 12:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1332</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Are microcredentials becoming a big deal?</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9171</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Microcredentials are not new.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 17:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1333</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Vocational education and training as a life jacket</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9168</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Young people not in employment, education or training (NEETs) are absent both from the labour market and the education sector, thus facing a high risk of professional, digital and social e&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 09:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1334</id>
            <title>Briefing note - An ally in the green transition</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9166</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The transition to a green – and more digital – economy and society will upend the job market and create new skill needs across sectors and occupations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 10:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1335</id>
            <title>Briefing note - High esteem but low participation</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9165</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2019, Cedefop launched a pan-European opinion survey on adult learning and continuing vocational education and training (CVET).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 11:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1336</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Championing the skills revolution</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9164</link>
            <description></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1337</id>
            <title>Briefing note - A fresh look at guidance practitioner professionalism</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9161</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cedefop’s briefing note offers new insights into how countries are modernising their career guidance systems and services.&amp;amp;nbsp;Defining practitioners’ role and recognising their compe&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 16:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1338</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Shifting our perspective on learning</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9159</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the world looks for a transition to a post-pandemic reality, changes are underway in many European companies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 03:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1339</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Analysing and comparing VET qualifications</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9158</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Vocational education and training (VET) qualifications must be relevant at national and local levels while opening the door to international comparability.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 11:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1340</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Trends, transitions and transformation</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9157</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Covid-19 pandemic is changing skill needs and reshaping jobs, while challenging our understanding and analysis of them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1341</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Apprenticeship: a pill for every ill?</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9155</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Following the financial crisis and the ensuing economic downturn in the past decade, apprenticeship sparked renewed interest among policy-makers both in Brussels and the EU Member States.&amp;amp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 11:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1342</id>
            <title>Briefing note - The EU’s port of call for VET</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9154</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Supporting vocational education and training, skills and qualification policies from concept to implementation: Cedefop highlights 2020-21&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1343</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Empowering people to cope with change</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9153</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the face of the current health crisis and the far-reaching labour market transformations it entails, the European Union and its Member States are taking action to provide all people in &lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 19:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1344</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Adult learning and continuing vocational education and training valued by Europeans</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9152</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insights from a pan-European opinion survey conducted by Cedefop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1345</id>
            <title>Briefing note - NQF developments 2019</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9150</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For years, the European qualifications framework (EQF) and national qualifications frameworks (NQFs) across Europe have helped build bridges across different countries and education and tr&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 13:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1346</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Online working and learning in the coronavirus era</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9148</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The coronavirus (Covid-19) pandemic has highlighted the vast opportunities of working and learning digitally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 10:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1347</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Apprenticeships for adults</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9147</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apprenticeships for adults are one of the policy solutions to the need for supporting adults willing to train, while broadening the skills base of the working population across Europe.&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1348</id>
            <title>Briefing note - On the move but not there yet</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9145</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;European policies on international mobility of students in initial vocational education and training (IVET) are working but more is needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 12:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1349</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Towards new horizons</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9144</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transition is the key word that marks the 2019 and 2020 policy framework in which Cedefop operates.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1350</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Not just new jobs: digital innovation supports careers</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9143</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is widely accepted that digital innovation is changing work environments and occupational profiles, impacting on people’s learning and work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 09:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1351</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Artificial or human intelligence?</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9140</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cedefop research shows that automation and artificial intelligence do not necessarily destroy, but rather transform jobs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 12:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1352</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Qualifications frameworks in Europe: 2018 developments.</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9139</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thirty nine European countries are currently developing 43 national qualifications frameworks (NQFs) which have reached different stages of implementation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1353</id>
            <title>Briefing note - The skills employers want!</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9137</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Analysing online job vacancies is a promising approach to identify&amp;amp;nbsp;emerging jobs and skill needs, as it offers rich real-time information about the skills employers seek.&amp;lt;/p&amp;amp;gt&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 13:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1354</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Preventing low skills through lifelong learning</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9136</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Integrated and well-tailored pathways for people to acquire or upgrade basic skills at different points in life are increasingly used to prevent skill gaps and skill shortages.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 08:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1355</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Setting sail for the future</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9135</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Helping to make vocational education and training fit for the future: Cedefop activities 2018-19&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 13:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1356</id>
            <title>Briefing note - What future for vocational education and training in Europe?</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9133</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To help in shaping future policies, a Cedefop project considers different routes and multiple options for&amp;amp;nbsp;vocational education and training (VET).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 08:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1357</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Cedefop’s European skills index: new tool for informed policy-making</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9132</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The European skills index is a monitoring tool, providing a snapshot of how countries’ skills systems perform. It depicts a complex reality in a single measure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1358</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Less brawn, more brain for tomorrow's workers</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9130</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Work environments in the near future are expected to feature more autonomy, less routine, more use of ICT, reduced physical effort and increased social and intellectual tasks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 13:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1359</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Reaching out to ‘invisible’ young people and adults</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9128</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Low qualifications, disengagement from education and training and long-term unemployment are interconnected phenomena and tend to cumulate throughout a person’s life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 09:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1360</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Qualifications frameworks in Europe 2017 developments</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9127</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As countries across Europe are pushing ahead with their national qualifications frameworks, Cedefop's briefing note examines the question of the frameworks’ added value and contributi&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 13:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1361</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Improving vocational education and training through data, analyses and exchanges</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9126</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The European Union’s economic recovery has strengthened.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1362</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Skills anticipation: looking to the future</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9124</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Skills anticipation can be a powerful policy tool for decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 08:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1363</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Looking back to look ahead</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9123</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the current framework for cooperation in vocational education and training (VET) approaches its 2020 expiry, Cedefop is now looking further ahead to stimulate the debate on European VET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 10:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1364</id>
            <title>Briefing note - People, machines, robots and skills</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9121</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Technological unemployment is a recurring theme, but joblessness in the digital age will depend on human, not artificial, intelligence.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 08:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1365</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Vocational education and training: bridging refugee and employer needs</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9120</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over the past two years, Europe has received an unprecedented number of refugees and asylum seekers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 12:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1367</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Qualifications frameworks in Europe</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9117</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As national qualifications frameworks (NQFs) are taking shape, their benefits become visible across the European Union.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1368</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Skill shortage and surplus occupations in Europe</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9115</link>
            <description>new description</description>
            <picturePath>assets\7208830f-d377-428d-942c-b8aecfb72d80.jpeg</picturePath>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 13:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1369</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Supporting training and learning abroad: the EU mobility scoreboard for initial VET</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9114</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mobility scoreboard takes stock of European countries&amp;amp;rsquo; provisions for learning abroad, offering a wealth of comparable information and examples of good practice.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 09:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1370</id>
            <title>Briefing note - Evolution of European skills systems</title>
            <link>https://www.cedefop.europa.eu/en/publications/9199</link>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The European skills index shows how national skills systems responded during the challenging period of 2015 to 2022.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <picturePath>assets\d241eb33-4b71-4155-9c57-ec0c7c05afd6.jpeg</picturePath>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:25:20 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1371</id>
            <title>title</title>
            <link>google.com</link>
            <description>description</description>
            <picturePath>assets\cf83f3c9-9e6e-44f4-be8a-579408c4d0cc.jpeg</picturePath>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:28:24 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <id>1372</id>
            <title>new title</title>
            <description>another description</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:29:25 +0200</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
